I am not a failure, professor. I'm not.
I am Mojo Jojo, a genius of scientific
intellect. Stop it. Stop laughing at me.
You think you're better than me just
because you wear a lab coat. That
doesn't make you special. Anyone can buy
a lab coat at Party City. No, it
doesn't. No, no, I don't have to prove
[__] You have to prove to me why a lab
coat makes you better. No, I don't care
if you have a bigger ass. Stop trying to
move the goalpost. You always do this.
>> What's wrong, my little monkey man? Did
you have yet another sexually charged
argument with the professor? You know
how terrible those are for your blood
pressure.
>> It's always him. [__] he called me
just to tell me how much of a loser I
am.
>> Darling, you are not a loser. Now, let's
go downstairs.
I made the boy's favorite beans on
toast.
I freaking hate beans on toast. Where's
the bacon and hash browns? I'm getting
ready to stab a [__] I like it. The
bread acts as a sponge and soaks up the
juice from the beans, making it nice and
squishy. Hey, Brick, did you know beans
are a superfood? Did you know I don't
give a [__] I'm just saying. If we eat
enough beans, we may finally be able to
defeat the Powerpuff Girls, says the one
who gets his ass kicked by weak ass
bubbles. Hey, Butch, I saw those
sugar-coated [__] heading to school
this morning. What do you say we
intercept them and show them who's the
real boss ass [__]
>> You're going to fight the Powerpuff
Girls. As in Townsville, as in they
won't be at home all day.
>> Obviously, dumbass monkey.
>> Interesting. Go cause destruction, my
evil children. But put on your jackets.
It's cold outside,
>> bro. Like, shut the hell up. Yeah,
you're doing like some full-on dad [__]
right now. You're not even our real dad.
Like, bro, you're a monkey. A literal
monkey. Someone get this chimpanzeee a
banana so he can put it up his monkey
butt.
>> Brick and Boomer, you're grounded for 2
days. Butch, we're taking away your
Android phone privileges because you
made monkey noises at Mojo Jojo.
>> That's cool. I got an iPhone.
>> They didn't mean it, my little monkey
man. Yes, they did. And let's face it,
I'm not even their real father. I'm just
a monkey. But maybe I can prove to them
that I am a true man if I steal Chemical
X.
It took God 7 days to create life, but
Professor Udonium was able to do it in
just one night with Chemical X. And when
I finally get my hands on that [__] I
mojo Jojo shall be one step closer to
world domination.
Damn professor, that ass looks like two
cereal boxes. Anybody could see that you
could cut diamonds with that cake. It
ain't just a dumb truck. It's a whole
ass garbage dump. Why must you be better
than me in every conceivable way? My
round curvy ass simply cannot compare to
such a finely sculpted butt crack. God,
I bet it's so hard for him to wipe. But
it's worth it and he knows it.
At long last, you and I finally meet.
Oh, you're so much more beautiful than I
ever imagined.
It's time for I, Mojo Jojo, to claim
what is rightfully mine up in this
[__] What? This vial is empty. This is
preposterous. This is absurd. It's
[__] It's the professor, my ultimate
rival. Or rather, this could be a
blessing in disguise. Yes, perhaps he's
even here to make some more of that
chemical X.
Well, it's 4:00 in the afternoon again.
Time to make some Chemical X.
He is making some, and I get to see how
he makes it. Are you giving me my gift
early, Santa? Have I been a good little
monkey boy?
>> Dear God, I didn't want to believe it.
Chemical X is just a vial of Professor
Utonium's sweat crap.
>> Mojo Jojo, did you get the Chemical X
yet?
>> No, but I saw how he makes it.
>> How so, honey bun?
>> [__] take a wild guess. I'm not
touching that thing until I have an oven
mitt.
>> Well, do you want me to come in and get
it?
>> No way. I don't want you touching that
thing either. Wait outside. I'll go look
around the house to see if there's
anything I can grab it with. I might
have to come back tomorrow.
>> I'm at the Taco Bell drive-thru. Do you
want the $5 or $7 lucha box?
>> What's the difference?
>> The $7 one comes with a drink.
>> Get that one. I want to compare the Baja
Blast with the Midnight One releasing
this summer. He just started dropping
another log. Now's the chance to move.
I'll call you back later.
>> Go, Bubble Gun.
>> Curses. I've been captured.
This is what you get for breaking into
my house, little monkey. You're lucky.
There are plenty of people who would pay
good money to be trapped in a bubble and
farted on by my big butt.
>> You won't get away with this, Professor.
Soon the entire world will know how to
make Chemical X. Everyone will have the
power you have. And when everyone is
God, no one is. You're not special. Did
I say you could talk, [__]
I have all the power. Mojo Jojo. People
will only know the truth if you get out
of that bubble, which you won't. Go
bubble ray.
H. Look at that. Now you're trapped
behind two bubbles.
>> That's it. I'm calling the cops. They
won't help you. You're evil. Him. Him.
Pick up. I Mojo Jojo. I'm in trouble.
>> Him. Him. Why aren't you answering me?
Are you okay? Oh no. Did the Powerpuff
Girls find you?
>> Rescue isn't coming. Mojo Jojo Joe. It's
over.
>> Yeah, it's just us and we are going to
kill you.
>> Thanks for the free Taco Bell. Now the
professor doesn't have to make us our
after school mac and cheese.
>> Girls, you are formally authorized to
kill on site.
>> I can't wait for Mojo Jojo to see all of
these bananas we bought for him.
>> Yeah, this is going to be so cool. Look,
here he comes. Hurry, pretend like we
don't hate him.
>> Well, what do we have here? A bundle of
bananas. Still carrying on with the
cringe monkey jokes. I see.
>> It's not a joke, Mojo Jojo. We bought
them for you. Because since you're a
monkey, you really like bananas.
>> You You did? But why? I thought you
hated me.
>> We do. But given the fact that we might
inherit the house after you die, Boomer
figured we should stay on your good side
so you don't take that away from us. So,
we got you some bananas.
Rick, that's the nicest thing anyone's
ever said to me. I would love to eat a
banana.